FELIX CARVAJAL

SKILLS

Knowledge in computer science and programming. I have experience in the area of web, desktop and mobile application development in frameworks like: Angular 2+, Javascript/TypeScript, C# (ASP.NET, .Net Core, .Net, Xamarin), Java EE (Spring, Hibernate), PHP (Laravel), Flutter, NativeScript. and Methodologies and flow works like: Agile, Scrum, TDD, DDD, S.O.L.I.D., KISS, DRY.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ministry of Finance and Public Administration, Santo Domingo— Software Developer

Feb 2018 - May 2018

- Backend C# ASP.NET MVC.
- Frontend Angular 6.
- DB MSSQL.

Concentra SRL, Santo Domingo— Software Developer

Sep 2018 - April 2019

- Backend C# ASP.NET MVC.
- Frontend Angular 6.
- DB MSSQL.

BM Cargo, Santo Domingo — Software Developer

Oct 2019 - Feb 2020

- Mobile App Developer in NativeScript.
- Back-end API Developer in C# (ASP.NET, Windows Forms, WPF).
- Frontend Developer Angular 7/8

Blue Coding LLC, EE.UU. (Miami, Florida) — Cross-platform Mobile Developer

Oct 2020 - Feb 2021 (Temporary Project)

• Mobile App Developer in Javascript (NativeScript-vue)

Utreee, Santo Domingo — Software Developer

Feb 2021 - Feb 2022

- Java EE (Spring, Tomcat, Java Android)
- PHP, Javascript, MySQL, Cordova Framework 7

Wepsys, Santo Domingo - Full-Stack Developer

Febrero 2022

• BackEnd (.Net 6, SQL Server, Docker)

- FrontEnd (Angular 12, Razor, React)
- Jira
- Github

EDUCATION

Universidad Autónoma de Santo Domingo — *Computer Science Degree*Agosto 2013

Conin/Infosyp - Development in C# (ASP.NET)
June 2016 - February 2017

Online Courses — Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Flutter, Xamarin, PHP (Laravel), ReactNative, Figma/AdobeXD, Android Kotlin,